we got to get on the same page. Enough of us have to get on the same page
because too many people talking are people who actually just want to be a politician themselves.
And so when they're speaking about politicians, they're just speaking from the point of view
of if it was me. That's it. So those of us who actually don't want to be a politician,
we got to get on the same page about what is required of us. I'm trying to understand
how people can't understand. So I'm going to keep saying it. I'm going to keep saying it until I
start seeing people saying it to other people. Because the fact of the matter is that a lot of
folks, they, and this is not new, but folks don't want to be free. They just want to be the boss.
Right? They just want to be the boss. And let me just tell you, as someone who has employed people,
people want to be the boss until they're the boss. Yeah. People want to be the boss until they're the
boss. And then they're like, Oh my gosh, I didn't know it was all this. So a lot of people, when they
are watching politicians, they're like, Oh, I want to be that. I want to be in charge. I want to be in
charge. When the truth is politicians should not be considered as in charge.
No, that is our first mistake. Our first mistake is operating as a society that requires folks to
tell us what to do, because then we give authority to people. And when you give authority to people,
you do very, you have a very difficult time being able to get them to do things on your behalf.
So it's very difficult in this dynamic to get anyone to show up in any kind of way,
because you have already said to them, we're not worthy. We're not worthy. So why would they?
Why would they bother? Why would they even care about what you think? All you do
is get them into position and they show you every single time
that they don't really care. Okay. You know what? I won't say every single time because there are a few
exceptions. However, people at this point, for the most part, and I say for the most part,
because there's always exceptions, folks go into politics because they know it's corrupt
because they don't want to keep being the source of the corruption. They don't want to be at the
bottom of the Ponzi scheme. They want to be at the top. Hold on. So a lot of people go into politics
so that they can make the decisions about how the scheme is going to work, not because they want to
dismantle the scheme. Now in a perfect, not even in a perfect, but in a very positive outcome,
Zora Mamdani would become some sort of spook by the door, so to speak. If you've never read the book
by Sam Greenlee by the same title, then you need to read it. So the same way that there are operatives
that are in places to infiltrate, to actually cause disruption for the good guys is a spook by the door
is there to actually cause disruption against the bad guys. Okay. A mole, so to speak. Now in a very
positive outcome, that would be the case. However, we don't know if that's the case yet.
And I know that there are people that are like, just watch. You'll see. I hope I see.
Baby, prove me wrong every day, Monday, Tuesday, Wednesday, Thursday, Friday, Saturday, Sunday,
Prove me wrong. I would love to be wrong. Baby, I'd love it. I would love to be wrong because it sucks
being right all the time about shit I can't change. Okay. It's very irritating.
You been in? Oh, no, you're not. So when we are talking about this person,
we're not speaking about the fact that he is a part of a system. And so many people have latched on
to the teeth of Mondani, of Mondani, Mondani, to the teeth of Mondani. Jordi, come here. Come here.
Quit playing with me. Jordi, come on. Come on. You want to go bark at them dogs. That's what you want
to do. You want to go bark at them dogs over there. No, we're not doing that right now. You're not
barking at the dogs. I know that's what you wanted to do. You wanted to go bark at the dogs.
So, you know, it's just that that's really where we need to get on the same page. If we could simply,
if we could simply just get on the same page about what we who are not elected officials expect
from elected officials, like that would be great. If we could stop telling folks not to critique or not
to challenge, guess what? Maybe that's not your ministry, but there is no reason. There is no reason
to be telling anybody not to critique or challenge a politician fairly. Now, an unfair critique is when
people say things like about their identity, right? So racist commentaries, sexist commentaries,
xenophobic commentary, xenophobic commentary. However, when we are acknowledging their political
ideology, when we are acknowledging the expectation for them to show up the way that they stepped up,
no, when we're expecting them to step up the way they showed up, these are all within the realm
of common sense and constructive criticism. We live in a nation that has convinced everybody,
I don't know when this happened, but that convinced you, you shouldn't be criticized.
And as somebody who sits up here and is criticized by you lot all day long, there's a, there's a very
valid reason to criticize somebody whose actions are not aligning with their words.
So we got to get on the same page. We got to get on the same page. Also, let's just clear something up.
Democrats are not leftists. Democrats are not leftist. And no, I wouldn't sit down with Momdani.
I don't want to spend any more time sitting down with politicians because they are dishonest.
And they're not necessarily dishonest outright, but a lot of times they are dishonest with themselves.
However, they, it's okay. When I was on the real, we would have to like interview reality TV people.
And I was always like, what are we doing? Like, why am I interviewing somebody on a show? That's a fake show
about the show. So like, we would be interviewing like housewives within the context of the show.
Like, man, this is fake. This is not real. This is not real. So I would be on the real and my face would be
so confused and stank and not, not, I'd be like, what am I doing right now? Like my master's degree
is on fire on the wall. Like I'm going to get home to a house burned down because I'm here wasting my
intellect interviewing a person pretending to be a part. Like what is this? This is not method acting.
What interviewing politicians be like, because you're not going to keep it a buck.
You're not going to keep it a buck for a myriad of reasons, right? You're not going to keep it a buck
because, um, you're not going to keep it a buck because you have security clearance, right? So
there's like confidential things that you can't tell us. You're not going to keep it a buck because
this is a country that runs on conspiracy. You're not going to keep it a buck because even if you
weren't the one doing it, if you rat on somebody else, they coming for you. So like, what's the
point? That's not my ministry. My ministry is decolonizing. My ministry is doing for others
what I was very fortunate to be able to do for myself. That is the goal to bring people out of
indoctrination and mental colonization and into truth. And I believe the only reason I was able
to do that was also because I had gone to therapy and had already done that for myself as a person.
So I had to get out of how me, Amanda had been indoctrinated
by narcissism, by codependency, by sexism, like these things that had affected my personality
outside of my ability. Right? So like when you're growing up, you are, there's nature and nurture.
So you, there's a certain level of nature, but then there's nurture. There's things that are
happening around you that are going to shape you. And then at a certain point, at a certain point,
at a certain point, you are able to identify, this is not natural for me. Like literally existing,
right? It's, it's killing me. And as I was growing up, existing was so hard. Like I remember writing
on in big red letters, just the words, just live and putting them on my closet door in my apartment
so that I could wake up every morning and see them and try to commit to just living. But then I realized
later in, later on in life that I was never going to be able to do that because I didn't even
understand the skin I was in. And because I was in a, a, a space, a competition space that was
counterintuitive to my actual being. So I was in Hollywood and yes, I'm an artist. I'm very gifted
in that realm, et cetera, but I am not a capitalist and I'm not an opportunist and I don't care about
fame. I'm not any of those things. So I was living, I was existing in an environment that was lacking
the nutrients that I need to actually be myself. So then you start creating all these other
methodologies to survive. Then I find out that, Oh, I am autistic. So this entire time that I've
been existing, these, all these things that I was ashamed of are actually just who I am.
I also learned all these things that I'm taking for granted are actually tools that will help me be
able to exist. You know, like sleep. Oh, I have to sleep. Like some people be like, I sleep when I
die. I, I can't play that game. I have to sleep. Oh, music. I'd be like, Oh yeah. You know, you can
change my mood in just one song. That is correct because your sensitivity is an audio sensitivity.
You have a music sensitivity. That is why you have an uncanny ability to no pitch. That's why you can
always tell a wrong note in a room. That's why you cannot hear disordinated sounds or it will drive
you crazy. So I'm just saying all these things because there is a correlation that I believe
took place within my ability to first decode myself and then be able to decode the world I'm in.
Because if you can decode yourself, which is an ego death, right? Then it ain't nothing
to make an ego death of the world because that's what you're being kept up in. You're being kept up
in this belief that this thing around you is so amazing. No, it's the thing beneath you. That's
amazing. It's the planet. It's the planet. That's amazing. It's the earth. That's amazing.
Okay. That's what's amazing. This other shit that they've created, all of this shit,
you know, innovation is interesting, but if it's not applied
practically, it's not applied consciously, then it simply is disruptive and it is destabilizing
and it is destructive. So hold on, let me block this person. So when I see the folks that are
so caught up in the minutiae of Democrats and Republicans, and I say minutiae because there is
an entire globe of people out here that exist in other ways. And you only care about that way
because you think that's the only thing that matters because that's what you're living in.
However, I will tell you that if you think that's the only thing that matters, then that means that's
the only thing you're going to know. And if you think that's all you need to know, then maybe you've
lost already. So we have to get on the same page. We have to understand the difference between those
who are in politics and those who are in the people. We have to understand that once you leave
the people and you go into politics, you are going to be dealt with differently and you should.
And if you're a real one, you understand that and you welcome it. You welcome it.
You say, I'm here for this. Come at me, bro. Someone said, allow Zoran to lead. Excuse me?
To lead people? No. Don't ask me again about Nicki Minaj and the Nigerians. Again,
we are in a position that was created. So everybody understands this is all of our responsibility
and I want us to get on the same page simply about that first and foremost,
that it's all of our responsibility. Hold on. Let me block this person to these accounts in India
with fake names and faces looking like black women harassing me. It's to be understood.
It has to be understood. You have to know when you're going into certain spaces, what is demanded
of you? And show up that way. I, I, again, I teach these kids art at a community center. So I know
they're going to try me. I'll tell you a little story. So this little girl in the class, the first
day of class, I asked everyone to give me a high five and she was like, no, I won't give you a high
five. And I said, why not? And she said, because I had, I'm tired. I don't feel like it. And I was like,
all right, well, you think about it and hopefully I will get an high five by the end of the day.
So I never got my high five. That was seven classes to go, seven classes ago. Okay. So now today in
class and she's great. Her art is always fascinating. She's very creative, very innovative. I love watching
what she's going to come up with. And today she blew me away again. So today she did it and she did her
art thing. And then, um, I was like, Oh, and I gave her a fist bump and she was like, Oh, aren't you
glad that, um, I say, you should be glad because I finally gave you a fist bump. And I said, Oh no,
baby, you should be glad that I offered you a fist bump after you were so rude to me the first day.
Ponytail. While I look over and my counselor, Ms. Keisha is over there. Snickering.
Ponytail. The reason I tell this story is because she did not realize the dynamics of the space we
were in. I know the dynamics of the space we're in. I know what's expected of me. I got to come in
there and I got to show up and teach these kids some art. I also need to be patient with them. I also
need to understand that they're going to try me in that regard. I also need to be ready
to stand on business. The only way I can stand on business is if I'm about the business.
So if I was coming in there on some bullshit, she could have come at me sideways and I shouldn't
have had nothing to say. Cause I'm not showing up. I am showing up and I did show up and I feel
like, that's where we have to understand. Sometimes people say, well, you know, you choose the path.
Like I remember when, um, certain websites were like, just trying to put personal shit about me
up on their page. And I'm like, this is my personal business. And I don't understand why you think it's
your right to put it up there. And they said, because you are a celebrity. And so you knew what
you were getting into. That is not the same. Okay. That is not the same as a politician who knows
that when they step into the realm as an elected official, they really answer or should be answering
to the people who elected them. I don't think you all grasp that. Like they are your employee.
Y'all understand that, right? Y'all understand that politicians are your employees. Are y'all aware
of this? You are paying for their livelihood. You got them the job, health insurance forever.
And she has a pension forever, not as the vice president. However, it's a loophole because it's
because of being a member of the Senate or no, the member of the house of representatives,
which all vice presidents are, they are the, the tie break. Well, they are the breaking vote.
So I just want to remind you that as Laurel says right here, our employees are robbing us blind.
Nancy Pelosi has made $200 million since she entered the house of representatives.
When they are sending money to Izzy, they are making money off of that. So again, all of this is real
and to suggest that questioning this is somehow harmful to working class is an attempt at folks
to use the term harm reduction. To allow the continued practice of corruption.
Because the reduction of harm will not happen to the group that they are claiming to care most about.
Politics has nothing to do with reducing that harm. In my heart of, in my, in my, in my best hope
for Zora Mamdani, in my, in my most optimistic, he is capitulating in all of these ways in order to try
to get something across the finish line that is irrevocable. That is the best case scenario that he's putting
on a face to slight of hand while he does other things that are disruptive to the status quo.
Best, best, best case scenario. We'll see. But most importantly, is that there has to be the we
in we'll see. We have to be on the same page. We have to operate as a proletariat. We have to kill
the ego. We have to kill the ego. We have to know the limits of our knowledge. We have to know the extent
of our efforts at education. We have to be honest with ourselves about these things in order to know
who to listen to, in order to know when to speak, and in order to know what actions to take.
Without this, you are simply just a voice in your own way of progress. Because right now,
there are a bunch of people sitting around saying, I'm tired of being the people.
I'm tired of being the people. I want to be the power. And it's those folks that I see saying,
don't question these folks. Let them do their job. Your job is to question. That is our job.
And anybody who says, I don't want to be the people no more. I want to be in power
is a politician, not a public servant. And what we need is a governance comprised of public servants.
And I hope that within my lifetime, we see that. So again, so here's someone said, you know,
people are going to be upset at seeing him compromise and disappointed and play the game,
which is literally being a politician. That is because we don't want politicians, sir.
He was elected. He gained his following by acting the opposite of politicians. So to see him lean into
this, Bush wear the same. They start wearing suits. To see them switch up. You know, I was in Grenada
and I was talking to my godfather and he was saying that, you know, he went to school, he went to
college with, um, the late great Walter Rodney, the current prime minister of St. Vince, uh, St.
Vincent, uh, Gonzalez, I can never, is it Gonzalez, but it's a V I can never remember. And I can't
remember the two other folks, but all of them, he said, when they were in school, were all radical.
And he said that at the end of school, when they went out into the world, Walter Rodney was the
only one who remained radical and he got assassinated. But the rest of them, he said,
he watched them become regular. He watched them become politicians. And I said, well, what do you
think is the reason they became regular? He said, because they realized that they were not going to be
able to meet their goals of ambition as radicals. Their ambition was greater than their radicalism.
Some of you all may not know what radicalism is. It sounds wild. Sounds crazy. The irony is that
radicalism is the most sane ideology out there. It is the most sane ideology out there. The time we're in
right now is a moment. One moment in time when I thought it was starting with me. Okay. Yes. Radicalism is the
most sane ideology out there. The person here who said, I don't know about that. That's because you don't know what
radicalism is. I'm sure. So again, we are in a moment of time. We have been so over trained to fear our
mortality that we only think about our life within the context of being alive. And the truth is,
it's a lot longer than you being here. So a toast. So someone in here said they think radicalism is an
extreme ideology. So for those of you who know what radicalism is, can you please illuminate within
the comments some of the ideologies of radicalism, leftist radicalism, specifically leftist radicalism.
Can you please illuminate some of the ideologies since it's so extreme while you're doing so? I'll name
some leftist radical ideology. Everyone can eat. Everyone has health care, even if they don't work.
Oh my God. Employees get to be a part of determining how they work. Taxes paid are applied
to services that uplift the wellness of the people. You're doing too much. Doing too much.
Corporations, in some cases, they don't exist at all. In other cases, they exist with heavy taxation.
Excuse me. They have limitations. They cannot do whatever they want to do. There's no money
exchange in government. This is radical. This is what a radical leftist believes. A radical leftist,
depending on how socialist you are, how communist you are, believes that any money that is being
created by the people should be used for the people. And yes, Trump is radical on the right.
He is an extremist. He is an extremist of Christian nationalism. With that, I'm going to try not to
eat ice cream tonight because your girl is very much a size large. Does anybody know anyone who can
alter some genes? I need to like, do you believe in our current democratic voting system? Nothing about
our voting system is democratic. Where do you all get this from? What about our voting system is
democratic? You didn't even get to choose the candidates for president. Like what? What about
our voting system is democratic? There's an electoral college. There's an electoral college. That electoral
college determines who the president is. So that means depending on what state you're in determines how
valuable your vote is. This is not, yeah, no, what I'm trying. Okay. I said alter, but I was being too
generous. What I really need is somebody to put a little extra fabric
down the side of these jeans. It's going to look like a tuxedo pant, but I'm fine with it
because the jean themselves is so dope. I got two pairs of jeans that are so dope, but they small
and I need them to get done right. Six months. No, people shouldn't be able to campaign longer than
three weeks. That's it. Three weeks. You should not be allowed to campaign. No, there's no, there's no
merch. There's no signs. None of that. Tell this Rachel person in here where she's at. Cause she
clearly don't know what it is. I want one moment in time. I mean, how do I envision that? I want you to
go watch the movie. No. That's what I want you to do. I want you to go watch the movie. No. 2012
starring Gael Garcia Bernal. It's a historical drama based on a play, but it is about the campaign in
Chile. Um, that, that ended up ousting Pinochet. So I want you to go watch that film. It's just two
pairs. Two pairs. Okay. So there's two pairs that need to be expanded, but then there's one pair that
needs to be, because I really was like, dang, I'm a big girl. And I got a 34 and ma'am, it's a 31.
Mm-hmm. Go back and watch No. The film is called No, literally N-O. There you go. She saw No in her
Latin studies democracy class. So don't say I didn't give you nothing. Go to amandaseals.com.
I will be in DC on December 2nd at Busboys and Poets for my book tour. I will be in
Baltimore on December 3rd with my book tour. So please make sure you RSVP, come on out, buy a book,
get it signed. All the good things and keep in the loop because I will be coming to Houston
on December 10th. I'll be in New Orleans on December 11th. I'll be in Atlanta on December 13th. And I will
be in Dallas on December 14th. Okay. I wish all of you all a great evening. Tell your friends who are
in DC and Baltimore that they need to come on out. All right. And I want you all again to go back and
watch. Go back and watch this episode of Amanda ranting. Okay. Go back and watch and understand
what I mean by we got to get on the same page. Nice y'all.